http://www.religiousministries.com/privacy-policy

About Us|Advertising OptionsCatholic VocationsCall to Religious MinstriesVocations in the ChurchCalendar of EventsRetreat HousesSponsor ProfilesRequest Vocation InformationAbout UsAdvertising Options Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyThis privacy statement describes the web practices and use of personal information on www.ReligiousMinistries.com, a service of The Catholic News Publishing Company. Protecting user's privacy has always been a main concern at ReligiousMinistries.com. RegistrationRegistration is not required to use this site. Users may review listing information for all communities, dioceses and organizations. Users may elect to contact vocation offices directly or contact the Catholic News Publishing Company offices to obtain information from several communities.Cookies and Web Logs ReligiousMinistries.com uses standard "cookie" technology and web server logs to collect information about how our web site is used. Cookies collect information on user sessions, but do not collect personal information such as email addresses. It is the policy of this site never to share information gathered by cookies. Linked Sites This site hosts numerous links to other sites. The privacy policies of linked sites may differ from that of ReligiousMinistries.com. Although we make an effort to make sure that proper privacy policies are intact on these sites, we accept no responsibility for their privacy policies. Security Policy ReligiousMinistries.com uses commercially accepted protocols and other security methods to protect a user's privacy. It is the policy of the site's operators to enforce this security policy to prevent unauthorized third parties from attempting to access personal information.
